(Raj:)I'm telling you, if xenon emits
ultraviolet light,
(Raj:)then those dark matter
discoveries must be wrong.
(Sheldon:)Yes, well, if we lived
in a world
(Sheldon:)where slow-moving xenon
produced light,
(Sheldon:)then you'd be correct.
(Sheldon:)Also, pigs would fly,
(Sheldon:)my derriere would produce
cotton candy,
and The Phantom Menace
would be a timeless classic.
(Raj:)Oh, you're so arrogant.
(Raj:)If you were a superhero,
(Raj:)your name would be
Captain Arrogant.
(Raj:)And you know
what your superpower would be?
(Raj:)Arrogance.
(Sheldon:)You're wrong again.
(Sheldon:)If my superpower were arrogance,
my name would be Dr. Arroganto.
(Howard(laughs):)I love watching Raj and Sheldon
try to work together.
(Leonard:)Yeah, it's like
if Alien and Predator decided
(Leonard:)to go partners
in a Jamba Juice.
(Raj:)Has it occurred to you
you're missing the big picture?
(Raj:)If you look at neutron
scattering data...
Oh, Penny?
(Sheldon:)Penny?
What's up?
(Sheldon:)Nothing. I just wanted
(Sheldon:)to make Raj stop talking.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)No, no, no.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)He won. Suck it up.
(Penny:)Well, I'd ask you guys
if you want dessert,
(Penny:)but I know Sheldon doesn't
eat dessert on Tuesdays.